

CONTACT ME AT

Krishna Saraswati Sadan, B wing, 2nd floor, Room No 18, Dilip Gupte Road, Mahim, Mumbai - 400 016

omkarh@gmail.com

omkar.info

in @omkarhatalkar

SKILLS SUMMARY

Frameworks:

- Django
- Flask
- CSS Bootstrap

Web Technologies:

- Wordpress
- Shopify
- HTML
- CSS
- Basic Java Script
- JQuery

Programming Languages:

Python

Version Control:

Git

Database:

 Relational database (i.e. PostgresSQL, MySQL, etc.)

IDE s/ Development Tools:

- Eclipse
- PyCharm
- Jupyter
- Sublime Text

Operating Systems:

- Linux
- Unix
- Windows
- MAC

Deployment Tools:

• Heroku

OMKAR HATALKAR

I'm a passionate, task-driven and committed software professional with 15+ years of industry experience. I've recently added Python Django Web Development to my repertoire and I'm eager to contribute my skills to an organization that is innovative and to gain experience in Django Web Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

Jan 2020 – Present

- Development of websites on Shopify and Wordpress
- Python Django Learning / Practice

Head of Web Development & IT

Five Stones Media House | May 2017 to Dec 2019

- 50+ websites created using Wordpress with full stack development starting from development to deployment and maintenance
- Preparing process and technical documentation
- Researching and recommending innovative web development solutions for clients

Freelance Web Developer

Apr 2016 - April 2017

• Developed Shopify websites for freelance clients

Web Developer

Right Turn | Nov 2015 - Mar 2016

 Front end work in HTML5, CSS and AngularJS and backend work in NodeJS ExpressJS and MongoDB

Senior Media Developer

LRN Technologies | Jul 2008 - Apr 2015

• Convert design templates or mocks into web pages that are responsive, semantic, scalable using HTML5 standards.

STRENGTHS

 Analytical thinking, Cross-functional knowledge, Quick learner, Driven by inspiration & hard-work, Flexible but straightforward nature.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor's Degree in Commerce (currently pursuing)
- SSC from Vinayaka Missions University